# Eiliya Abedianamiri

Vancouver, BC V6Z 2S1 iliaabedianamiri@gmail.com (778) 862-7477

Hi, my name is Eiliya (Ilia). I am an international student enrolling in the Full-Stack Web Development Diploma at BCIT. I have more than five years of experience in web development and coding and mainly use PHP and Node.js. I also tend to be more specialized in the back-end than front-end, but I'm capable of doing both. I am also familiar with CMS such as: WordPress and Drupal.

I am a detailed-oriented person and always care about my work by having integrity and precision throughout the whole process. I also believe that working as a team is better than being solo because a team can bring creative ideas to the table and allow the company to choose better. Therefore, having strong communication skills is necessary to engage in working with a team effectively.

Besides, learning new things is critical for working on current projects because employees should be ready to adapt to upcoming changes in this industry. We don't want to get stuck in the same ways that we have been using for an extended time while newer technologies are growing so fast, and we should use better solutions to get better results.

# Work Experience

# **Freelance Web App Developer**

Freelancer.com - Vancouver, BC May 2021 to June 2021

I used to work as a freelancer at freelancer.com as a web developer. I created a web-based bot for one of my customers using my own PHP Framework (Witcher), Selenium, HTML&CSS, and JavaScript (jQuery). It is available for the public on my Github as a repository.

#### **Private Web Developer**

An Individual Client – Tehran September 2019 to Current (On Call)

An individual hired me as his personal developer to develop his private projects. I have been developing, debugging, and managing the projects. The main technologies I've been using are: PHP (mainly OOP and cURL), Laravel, JavaScript (jQuery, Ajax, JSON), Node.js, React, MySQL (phpMyAdmin), cPanel, Linux, and Windows Servers (Firewalls, DNS Management,...), and APIs.

Moreover, I had been vastly using Selenium (a portable framework for testing web applications).

During this period, I was debugging applications written in Node.js and raw-jQuery as well. Also, I got familiar enough with bank payment processes and digital currency payment process and their integration with a web application (Web3).

## **Web Application Developer**

Radin Hamkaran Behta Co.

June 2018 to June 2019

I was an unpaid intern at the company, gaining knowledge and experience in C# and ASP.NET.

Company's Overview: Radin Hamkaran Behta Co. has been founded in 2010 and registered in 2011. By employing experienced and experts in the BIM field, our main goal is to design, implement and develop modern BIM-based engineering and managerial systems.

#### Education

# DCS / DEC in Full-Stack Web Development

British Columbia Institute of Technology - Vancouver, BC From July 2021 to Present

# **Technology**

Heritage Woods Secondary School - Anmore, BC

From September 2020 to June 2021

#### Skills

•	PHP	(5	vears)

• Laravel (2 years)

• MySQL (5 years)

Node.js (2 years)

• React (1 year)

• JavaScript (3 years)

• ¡Query (3 years)

• AJAX (4 years)

• HTML5 (6 years)

• XML (4 years)

• .NET (1 year)

• C# (2 years)

 Microsoft Windows Server (4 years)

• Python (Less than 1 year)

• Java (1 year)

• SQL (4 years)

• Microsoft SQL Server

CentOS (5 years)

• Linux (6 years)

VMWare (6 years)

• VPN (4 years)

• Docker (1 year)

• Bootstrap (6 years)

• CSS (6 years)

• GitHub (4 years)

• Git (1 year)

• APIs (4 years)

• REST (2 years)

• Agile (Less than 1 year)

• WordPress (2 years)

• R (Less than 1 year)

• Selenium (3 years)

## Languages

• Farsi - Expert

• English - Expert

#### Projects

#### Witcher - PHP Framework

https://github.com/iliaamiri/WitcherPhpFramework 2017 - current

Witcher is a Framework in PHP coded by me. I created my own Framework using raw PHP, so this framework uses few libraries, such as default libraries of PHP and some plug-ins specific to projects.

- It uses the MVC software architecture (Model, View, Controller).
- It is compatible with PHP 7.0 or higher.

#### **Lottery Game Website**

https://github.com/iliaamiri/A-Lottery-Game-Website 2018

A lottery game webapp has a backend code in PHP (using Witcher Framework), and simple front-ends using basic HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I coded this website for an individual client of mine back in 2018.

#### Khakbaz Md. Private Clinic Website

https://github.com/iliaamiri/DrKhakbaz-PrivateClinic-Website 2017

Dr. Khakbaz was an Iranian ophthalmologist who was requesting a business advertising website for her clinic. I used PHP to code this website. It is semi-static, including a simple admin panel.

# Basaz Construction Ltd. Website (Basaz.ca)

(For my client's privacy, I couldn't disclose the source code on my GitHub repository) 2021 – current Basaz Construction Inc. will be a building renovation and a construction project management firm in Canada. It will be responsible for the day-to-day oversight of a building renovations including; management of vendors, trades, and the communication of information to all involved parties throughout the course of a construction project.

## Profile Links

https://github.com/iliaamiri

https://www.linkedin.com/in/eiliya-abedianamiri-b4a093203/

# Readings

# **OWASP Web Security Testing Guide v4**

By the OWASP® Foundation • Read in 2018

# Applied training in C# programming language (in Farsi)

By Asadollah Shahbahrami and Erfan Zidehsaraei • Read in 2016

#### Additional Information

Some of my hobbies are gaming, watching movies, and researching on cybersecurity.